Terms and Conditions for Wane Thunder Icon Pack
Effective Date: April 1, 2026

These Terms and Conditions ("Terms") govern your use of the Wane Thunder Icon Pack application ("Application"), developed by Basu Apps ("Company", "we", "us", or "our"). Wane Thunder Icon Pack is an icon pack customization application for Android devices that allows users to apply custom icons, wallpapers, and customize their device launcher. By using the Application, you agree to comply with these Terms. If you do not agree with any part of these Terms, you may not access or use the Application.

1. License
Basu Apps grants you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable, revocable license to download, install, and use the Wane Thunder Icon Pack application for personal, non-commercial use on your Android device, in accordance with these Terms. The icon packs, wallpapers, and associated resources included in this application are for personal use only.

2. Application Features
Wane Thunder Icon Pack provides the following features:

Icon Pack Application: Apply custom icons to supported Android launchers
Wallpaper Gallery: Browse, preview, and apply wallpapers to your device
Icon Request: Request missing icons for your installed applications
Premium Features: Access to premium icon requests and additional features through in-app purchases
Launcher Integration: Integration with various Android launchers including Kustom, Nova, Action, and others
Muzei Support: Live wallpaper integration with Muzei app

3. User Responsibilities
By using the Application, you agree to:

Use the Application in compliance with all applicable laws and regulations.
Not modify, decompile, reverse engineer, or disassemble the Application or its icon packs.
Not use the Application for any illegal or unauthorized purposes, such as infringement of intellectual property rights.
Not redistribute, sell, or use the icons or wallpapers for commercial purposes without explicit written permission.
Not engage in any activity that interferes with or disrupts the Application or its licensing verification system.
Not attempt to bypass or circumvent the Google Play license verification system.
Not submit fraudulent icon requests or abuse the icon request system.

4. Ownership and Intellectual Property
All rights, titles, and interests in and to the Application, including all intellectual property rights, belong to the Company. The icons, designs, graphics, wallpapers, and associated software are protected by copyright, trademark, and other applicable laws. You do not acquire any ownership rights by downloading or using the Application. The icon packs are the original work of Basu Apps and may not be used outside of this Application without permission.

5. In-App Purchases
Wane Thunder Icon Pack may offer in-app purchases for premium features, including but not limited to:

Premium icon requests with faster processing
Additional icon packs or wallpaper collections
Ad-free experience (if applicable)

All purchases are processed through Google Play Billing. By making a purchase, you agree to Google Play's terms of service. Refunds are subject to Google Play's refund policy.

6. Icon Requests
Users may request icons for applications that are not currently included in the icon pack. Icon requests are subject to the following terms:

Requests are reviewed and may be accepted or rejected at the sole discretion of Basu Apps
Premium icon requests receive priority processing
Icon requests are not guaranteed to be fulfilled
Requested icons will be included in future updates if approved
Abuse of the icon request system may result in suspension of this feature

7. Google Services
The Application uses the following Google services to provide core functionality:

Google Play Billing Library: For processing in-app purchases
Google Play Licensing: For verifying legitimate app installations
Google Play In-App Review API: For facilitating app reviews
Muzei API: For live wallpaper functionality

By using the Application, you agree to Google's terms of service and privacy policies for these services.

8. Third-Party Services and SDKs
The Application uses the following third-party SDKs and services to provide additional functionality:

Kustom API: For integration with Kustom launcher
Glide Image Loading Library: For efficient image loading
OkHttp: For network communications
WorkManager: For background task management
AndroidX Libraries: For core Android functionality

By using the Application, you agree to the terms of service and privacy policies of these third-party providers.

9. Modifications to the Application
We reserve the right to modify, update, or discontinue the Application (or any part of it) at any time without notice. This includes adding or removing icon packs, wallpapers, features, or changing the pricing of in-app purchases. We are not liable to you or any third party for any modifications, suspensions, or discontinuations of the Application.

10. Disclaimer of Warranties
The Application is provided on an "AS IS" and "AS AVAILABLE" basis without warranties of any kind, whether express or implied. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, we disclaim all warranties, including but not limited to implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, and non-infringement.

We do not warrant that:

The Application will meet your requirements or expectations.
The Application will be compatible with all Android devices and launchers.
The Application will be uninterrupted, error-free, or secure.
Any defects or errors in the Application will be corrected.
The licensing verification system will be available at all times.
Icon requests will be fulfilled within a specific timeframe.

11. Limitation of Liability
To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, we will not be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, or consequential damages arising out of or in connection with the use or inability to use the Application. This includes, but is not limited to, damages for loss of profits, data, or goodwill, or any damages resulting from the inability to apply icons or wallpapers, or failed icon requests.

In no event shall our total liability exceed the amount you paid (if any) to use the Application.

12. Termination
We may terminate or suspend your access to the Application at our sole discretion, without prior notice or liability, for any reason, including but not limited to your breach of these Terms, violation of licensing requirements, unauthorized use of icon packs, abuse of the icon request system, or fraudulent activity.

Upon termination, your right to use the Application will cease immediately. All provisions of these Terms that by their nature should survive termination will survive, including ownership provisions, warranty disclaimers, and limitations of liability.

13. Privacy
Your use of the Application is also governed by our Privacy Policy, which explains how we collect, use, and share your information. Please review the Privacy Policy carefully before using the Application. The Privacy Policy includes information about:

Data collection and use
Google services and third-party services and their privacy policies
Your data rights
Data sharing practices

14. License Verification
Wane Thunder Icon Pack uses Google Play Licensing to verify that the app was downloaded from the Google Play Store. This verification process requires an active internet connection. By using the Application, you agree to this license verification process. Attempts to bypass or circumvent this verification may result in termination of your access to the Application.

15. Governing Law
These Terms and your use of the Application are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the country in which the Company is located, without regard to its conflict of law principles.

16. Changes to These Terms
We may update these Terms from time to time to reflect changes in the Application or applicable laws. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the updated Terms within the Application or on our website. Your continued use of the Application after the changes take effect constitutes your acceptance of the updated Terms.

17. Contact Us
If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us at:

Basu Apps
App: Wane Thunder Icon Pack
Email: oxoytpoint@gmail.com
